Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪When your lies and indifference♪
♪عندما تكذب ولا مبالاتك♪
♪Pierce my heart and shatter it♪
♪اخترق قلبي وحطمه♪
♪All my piety and persistence♪
♪كل تقواي ومثابرتي♪
♪Are torn apart, turning into bubbles in the air♪
♪تتمزق وتتحول إلى فقاعات في الهواء♪
♪When my fairy tale is broken by you♪
♪عندما تحطم حكايتي الخيالية بسببك♪
♪Turning into nightmares that haunt me♪
♪تتحول إلى كوابيس تطاردني♪
♪I decide to break free from your shackles♪
♪قررت أن أتحرر من قيودك♪
♪No longer swallowing the poison apple♪
♪ لم يعد يبتلع تفاحة السم ♪
♪You fed me♪
♪لقد أطعمتني♪
♪I burn the fairy tale, rewrite the role♪
♪أحرق الحكاية الخيالية، وأعيد كتابة الدور♪
♪Reborn as a resolute me♪
♪ولدت من جديد كشخصية حازمة♪
♪I have broken free from your shackles♪
♪لقد تحررت من قيودك♪
♪Throwing away that poison apple♪
♪رمي تلك التفاحة المسمومة♪
♪You fed me♪
♪لقد أطعمتني♪
[Love Conspiracy]
[مؤامرة الحب]
[Adapted from Enhenzhai's novel, Madam, No Mercy for Scum]
[مقتبس من رواية إينهينزهاي، سيدتي، لا رحمة للحثالة]
[Episode 22]
[الحلقة 22]
I'm here to warn Zhizhi to be careful of the people around her.
أنا هنا لأحذر Zhizhi من توخي الحذر من الأشخاص المحيطين بها.
What is going on here?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Zhizhi,
تشيزي،
this was sudden.
لقد كان هذا مفاجئا.
Let me explain everything later.
دعني أشرح كل شيء لاحقًا.
Zhizhi,
تشيزي،
this isn't Ziming's fault.
هذا ليس خطأ زيمينغ.
I asked him
سألته
to keep it secret.
للحفاظ على سريته.
Ziming
زيمينج
will be the group's successor.
سيكون خليفة للمجموعة.
You know about the internal power struggles,
أنت تعرف عن صراعات القوة الداخلية،
don't you?
أنت , لا؟
I'm just clearing the path for him.
أنا فقط أقوم بتطهير الطريق له.
Mr. Ye,
السيد يي،
you surely know how to strategize.
من المؤكد أنك تعرف كيفية وضع الاستراتيجيات.
If we secure the agency rights for Drizzt this time,
إذا حصلنا على حقوق الوكالة لدريزت هذه المرة،
according to our agreement,
وفقا لاتفاقنا،
it'll be a win-win situation.
سيكون هذا وضعًا مربحًا للجانبين.
You and Ziming grew up together.
لقد نشأت أنت وزيمينغ معًا.
You're close.
أنت قريب.
Once he takes over,
بمجرد توليه المسؤولية،
I'm sure the collaboration between you two
أنا متأكد من التعاون بينكما
will be successful.
سوف تكون ناجحة.
So
لذا
I should thank you. Is that it?
يجب أن أشكرك. هل هذا كل شيء؟
When we talk about the people around her,
عندما نتحدث عن الأشخاص من حولها،
you, the one set to marry her,
أنت، الشخص الذي سيتزوجها،
are that person.
هل هو ذلك الشخص؟
You should be more concerned
ينبغي عليك أن تكون أكثر قلقا
who the people around you really are.
من هم الأشخاص من حولك حقًا؟
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Don't you know what I mean?
ألا تعرف ماذا أقصد؟
Then I'll be blunt.
إذن سأكون صريحا.
You are not Ji Baijian!
أنت لست جي بيجيان!
You've been living under his name
لقد كنت تعيش تحت اسمه
all these years.
كل هذه السنوات.
So who are you really?
فمن أنت في الحقيقة؟
Since everyone's here, why don't you
بما أن الجميع هنا، لماذا لا؟
explain everything?
شرح كل شيء؟
Cat got your tongue?
هل حصلت القطة على لسانك؟
Mr. Ye,
السيد يي،
I planned to
لقد خططت لذلك
show you this document after the meeting.
سأعرض لك هذه الوثيقة بعد الاجتماع.
But since Mr. Ji is here,
ولكن بما أن السيد جي موجود هنا،
let's all
دعونا جميعا
get reacquainted with Ji Baijian.
التعرف مجددًا على جي بايجيان.
This report
هذا التقرير
contains an DNA analysis comparing
يحتوي على تحليل الحمض النووي للمقارنة
the Ji Baijian from eight years ago
جي بايجيان من ثماني سنوات مضت
with the man standing before us.
مع الرجل الواقف أمامنا.
[Regarding the Paternity Relationship Between Ji Baijian and Ji Yunlei]
[فيما يتعلق بعلاقة الأبوة بين جي بيجيان وجي يونلي]
He shares no blood relation with Ji Yunlei.
ليس لديه أي علاقة دم مع جي يونلي.
So who are you?
فمن أنت؟
This is strange.
هذا غريب.
Wei Ziming, what does this have to do with you?
وي زيمينغ، ما علاقة هذا بك؟
You investigated me?
هل حققت معي؟
Tit for tat.
العين بالعين.
You investigated me too, didn't you?
لقد قمت بالتحقيق معي أيضًا، أليس كذلك؟
Ji Baijian.
جي بيجيان.
May I call you that?
هل يجوز لي أن أناديك بهذا؟
Nice move.
خطوة جميلة.
I won't disturb your meeting.
لن أزعج اجتماعك.
I'm leaving.
انا ذاهب.
Zhizhi.
تشيزهي.
Zhizhi!
تشيزهي!
Ziming!
زيمينج!
I'll take this opportunity
سأستغل هذه الفرصة
to introduce you to everyone.
لأقدمك للجميع.
They'll support your work better.
وسوف يدعمون عملك بشكل أفضل.
Come on, have a seat.
تعال، اجلس.
No.
لا.
Let's discuss this another day.
دعونا نناقش هذا في يوم آخر.
Wait...
انتظر...
Let's end the meeting here.
دعونا ننهي الاجتماع هنا.
Everyone can leave now.
الجميع يمكنه المغادرة الآن.
Ziming, I called out
زيمينغ، لقد اتصلت
for your own good.
من أجل مصلحتك.
Do you have any idea
هل لديك أي فكرة
how I've felt
كيف شعرت
since learning you're my son?
منذ أن علمت أنك ابني؟
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
What kind of father wouldn't help his son?
ما هو نوع الأب الذي لا يساعد ابنه؟
Everything I've done
كل ما فعلته
is to secure your position
هو تأمين موقفك
within the group.
ضمن المجموعة.
I'm clearing the path for you.
أنا أفسح الطريق لك.
I did this not just for the group,
لقد فعلت هذا ليس فقط من أجل المجموعة،
but for Zhizhi.
ولكن بالنسبة لـ Zhizhi.
Kid,
طفل،
haven't you heard the saying
ألم تسمع المثل
"Great achievers don't fuss over minor details"?
"أصحاب الإنجازات العظيمة لا يهتمون بالتفاصيل الصغيرة"؟
A real man
رجل حقيقي
can't afford
لا أستطيع تحمل التكاليف
to be swayed by these romantic sentiments.
للتأثر بهذه المشاعر الرومانسية.
When did you start investigating Ji Baijian?
متى بدأت التحقيق في جي بايجيان؟
Who is he, really?
من هو حقا؟
A while ago.
منذ فترة.
Something made me suspicious,
شيء جعلني أشك،
so I looked into him.
لذلك نظرت إليه.
Is it
هل هو
related to Ji Baijian?
ذات صلة ب جي بيجيان؟
Regarding the photo you asked me to look into last night,
بخصوص الصورة التي طلبت مني أن أنظر إليها الليلة الماضية،
it's confirmed to be a photo of Ye Xiaoting and his son.
تم التأكد من أن الصورة هي لـ Ye Xiaoting وابنه.
He might be your nephew,
ربما يكون ابن أخيك
Ye Shengheng.
يي شينغينغ.
The fact that I adopted you
حقيقة أنني تبنيتك
has been a secret all these years.
لقد كان سرا طوال هذه السنوات.
And we kept this confidential
وحافظنا على هذا السر
to assist the police
لمساعدة الشرطة
with Ye Xiaoting's case.
مع قضية Ye Xiaoting.
How did Wei Ziming find out about it?
كيف عرف وي زيمينغ بهذا الأمر؟
I think he must have noticed me
أعتقد أنه يجب أن يكون قد لاحظني
visiting my parents' graves
زيارة قبر والدي
at the cemetery.
في المقبرة.
Wei Ziming is quite sharp.
وي زيمينغ حاد جدًا.
I'll have Yin Qin keep digging into him.
سأطلب من يين تشين الاستمرار في الحفر فيه.
The timing and motive behind his mother
التوقيت والدافع وراء والدته
sending him to an orphanage
إرساله إلى دار للأيتام
makes me feel suspicious.
يجعلني أشعر بالشك.
Wei Ziming
وي زيمينج
is Ye Taiting's son,
هو ابن يي تايتينغ،
yet he was sent to an orphanage
ومع ذلك تم إرساله إلى دار للأيتام
and raised by the Song family.
وترعرع على يد عائلة سونغ.
His backstory
قصته الخلفية
could be crucial
قد يكون حاسما
to obtaining criminal evidence
للحصول على أدلة جنائية
against Ye Taiting.
ضد يي تايتينغ.
But the rough gemstones incident was too long ago.
لكن حادثة الأحجار الكريمة الخام كانت منذ زمن طويل.
We can't do much about Ye Taiting for now.
لا يمكننا أن نفعل الكثير بشأن Ye Taiting في الوقت الحالي.
My gut tells me
حدسي يقول لي
he was involved
لقد كان متورطا
in my parents' car crash.
في حادث سيارة والدي.
If we can connect Ye Taiting
إذا تمكنا من ربط Ye Taiting
to the crash through Wei Ziming,
إلى الحادث من خلال وي زيمينغ،
we might finally bring him to justice.
ربما نتمكن أخيرًا من تقديمه للعدالة.
It would bring my parents peace.
وهذا من شأنه أن يجلب السلام لوالدي.
But he knows your identity now.
لكنّه يعرف هويتك الآن.
He'll make a move against you.
سوف يتحرك ضدك.
You need to be careful.
يجب عليك أن تكون حذرا.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I've made the first move,
لقد قمت بالخطوة الأولى،
and I never fight unprepared.
وأنا لا أقاتل أبدًا دون استعداد.
So what's your plan?
إذن ما هي خطتك؟
Since my cover is blown,
منذ أن تم كشف غطائي،
I'll catch Ye Taiting off guard.
سأمسك يي تايتينغ على حين غرة.
My father, Ye Xiaoting,
والدي، يي شياو تينغ،
founded Starlight Group.
أسس مجموعة ستارلايت.
Doesn't that entitle me
ألا يمنحني هذا الحق؟
to be the successor of Starlight Group?
ليكون خليفة لمجموعة ستارلايت؟
Good.
جيد.
Then I'll
ثم سأفعل
cooperate with you.
التعاون معك.
I'll stir up public opinion
سأثير الرأي العام
about the rough gemstones incident.
حول حادثة الأحجار الكريمة الخام.
And we'll
وسنفعل
point all fingers
أشر بكل أصابعك
at Ye Taiting.
ويي تايتينغ.
A two-pronged attack
هجوم مزدوج
should throw him off balance.
يجب أن يخرجه عن توازنه.
You uselss fools!
أيها الحمقى لا فائدة منكم!
You told me Ye Shengheng was missing!
لقد أخبرتني أن Ye Shengheng كان مفقودًا!
That he'd been dead
أنه كان ميتا
for years!
لسنوات!
And now?
و الآن؟
He's been right under my nose
لقد كان تحت أنفي مباشرة
as Ji Baijian all this time!
مثل جي بايجيان طوال هذا الوقت!
And I was like a fool
وكنت مثل الأحمق
and didn't notice at all!
ولم ألاحظ على الإطلاق!
Look what you've done!
انظر ماذا فعلت!
Mr. Ye, please calm down.
السيد يي، من فضلك اهدأ.
This is my fault.
هذا خطئي.
I wasn't cautious enough.
لم أكن حذرا بما فيه الكفاية.
I got tricked by Ji Yunlei.
لقد تم خداعي من قبل جي يونلي.
But now Ziming has found out the truth.
ولكن الآن اكتشف زيمينغ الحقيقة.
We still have time to be on guard.
لا زال لدينا الوقت لنكون على أهبة الاستعداد.
Listen,
يستمع،
Ji Baijian
جي بيجيان
might be doing this
ربما يفعل هذا
not just for the Ji family,
ليس فقط لعائلة جي،
but also for his parents!
ولكن أيضا لوالديه!
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
I need to ask you something.
أريد أن أسألك شيئا.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
Are you Ji Baijian or someone else?
هل أنت جي بيجيان أو أي شخص آخر؟
Who did I legally marry?
من تزوجت قانونيا؟
Why have you been hiding everything
لماذا كنت تخفي كل شيء؟
from me and lying?
مني والكذب؟
I don't even know who you are.
انا لا اعرف حتى من انت .
Don't tear that up!
لا تمزقها!
Ji Baijian,
جي بيجيان,
you deceived me once,
لقد خدعتني مرة واحدة،
and I retaliated.
ورددت.
I thought we were even.
اعتقدت أننا متساويين.
But I didn't know
ولكنني لم اعرف
even your identity was fake when we married.
حتى هويتك كانت مزورة عندما تزوجنا.
How much else have you been lying about?
ما هو مقدار الكذب الذي كذبت بشأنه؟
Right now, I am Ji Baijian.
في الوقت الحالي، أنا جي بايجيان.
I'm not lying.
أنا لا أكذب.
Ji Yunlei has legal adoption papers.
لدى Ji Yunlei أوراق التبني القانوني.
Adoption papers?
أوراق التبني؟
Ji Yunlei adopted you.
تبناك جي يونلي.
Then who were you originally?
إذن من كنت في الأصل؟
Tell me,
أخبرني،
who are you?
من أنت؟
Before I became Ji Baijian,
قبل أن أصبح جي بيجيان،
I was Ye Shengheng.
كنت يي شينغينغ.
Ye Xiaoting's son.
ابن يي شياو تينغ.
Why did you change from Ye Shengheng
لماذا تغيرت من يي شنغ هينج؟
to Ji Baijian?
إلى جي بيجيان؟
How did you go from being Ye Xiaoting's son
كيف تحولت من كونك ابن يي شياوتينغ؟
to Ji Yunlei's son?
لابن جي يونلي؟
The real Ji Baijian is dead.
جي بايجيان الحقيقي مات.
My real father was Ye Xiaoting,
والدي الحقيقي كان يي شياوتينغ،
Ye Taiting's older brother.
الأخ الأكبر لـ Ye Taiting.
Twenty years ago, our family was in a car crash.
منذ عشرين عامًا، تعرضت عائلتنا لحادث سيارة.
My parents died in that accident.
لقد مات والداي في هذا الحادث.
I got saved by Ji Yunlei by chance.
لقد تم انقاذي بواسطة جي يونلي بالصدفة.
Mom! Dad!
أمي! أبي!
Wake up!
استيقظ!
Ye Shengheng!
يي شينغينغ!
Mrs. Ye.
السيدة يي.
Xiaoting. Xiaoting!
شياوتينج. شياو تينغ!
He had me undergo the surgery
لقد أجرى لي عملية جراحية
and kept me protected abroad.
وأبقاني محميًا في الخارج.
Be careful not to get it wet.
كن حذرا حتى لا تبتل.
Keep your diet light.
حافظ على نظامك الغذائي خفيفًا.
Alright. Thank you.
حسناً، شكراً لك.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
You do look like my son Baijian.
أنت تبدو مثل ابني بايجيان.
Kid,
طفل،
the accident damaged your face.
لقد تسبب الحادث في تلف وجهك.
The doctors performed reconstructive surgery.
أجرى الأطباء عملية جراحية ترميمية.
You might look a little different now.
ربما تبدو مختلفًا قليلًا الآن.
It'll take some getting used to.
سوف يستغرق الأمر بعض الوقت للتكيف.
This isn't me.
هذا ليس انا.
This isn't me at all!
هذا ليس أنا على الإطلاق!
It's not me!
إنه ليس أنا!
This isn't me!
هذا ليس انا!
Where are my mom and dad?
أين أمي وأبي؟
Where did they go?
أين ذهبوا؟
They're dead!
لقد ماتوا!
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
I am your dad.
انا والدك
You are my son.
أنت ابني.
Your name is Ji Baijian.
اسمك جي بيجيان.
You must avenge your parents.
يجب عليك الانتقام لوالديك.
Remember?
يتذكر؟
From then on, I was no longer Ye Shengheng.
منذ ذلك الحين، لم أعد يي شينغ هينغ.
I became Ji Yunlei's son, Ji Baijian.
لقد أصبحت ابن جي يونلي، جي بيجيان.
I gained a father's love,
لقد حصلت على حب الأب،
but I was also burdened with his hatred.
ولكنني كنت أيضًا مثقلًا بكراهيته.
So I promised him
فوعدته
I would avenge his wife.
سأنتقم لزوجته.
Zhizhi,
تشيزي،
I never told you any of this
لم أخبرك بأي شيء من هذا
because
لأن
it's my deepest shame.
إنه عارى الأعمق.
Haven't you always asked who I really am?
ألم تسألني دائمًا من أنا حقًا؟
Actually, I don't even know myself.
في الواقع، أنا لا أعرف نفسي حتى.
♪Baby, asleep? Don't reply♪
♪حبيبي، نائمة؟ لا ترد♪
The name Ji Baijian wasn't mine.
الاسم جي بايجيان لم يكن لي.
This face isn't mine.
هذا الوجه ليس وجهي.
♪Just a conversation with you, left to float by♪
♪مجرد محادثة معك، تركتها لتطفو♪
And this life was never mine.
وهذه الحياة لم تكن لي أبداً.
♪Baby, changed? To me it's all the same♪
♪حبيبي، هل تغيرت؟ بالنسبة لي، الأمر نفسه.
I... I've been gathering evidence.
أنا... لقد كنت أجمع الأدلة.
I wanted to figure everything out about myself first
أردت أن أعرف كل شيء عن نفسي أولاً
and then come to you
ثم يأتي إليك
with a proper explanation,
مع شرح مناسب،
a satisfactory answer.
إجابة مرضية.
I didn't expect you
لم اتوقعك
to come asking all this today.
لأتي وأطلب كل هذا اليوم.
♪Won't beg for you to stay by my side♪
♪لن أتوسل إليك للبقاء بجانبي♪
♪Yet through the pain, I'll never leave your side♪
♪ومع ذلك، من خلال الألم، لن أترك جانبك أبدًا♪
♪It feels just like an illusion♪
♪إنه يبدو وكأنه مجرد وهم♪
So keep...
لذلك إستمر...
Keep this.
احتفظ بهذا.
♪Hold me tight. Don't let go of this dream♪
♪احتضني بقوة. لا تدع هذا الحلم يفلت منك♪
Alright?
على ما يرام؟
♪I will wait and embrace what's yet to be♪
♪سأنتظر وأحتضن ما هو قادم♪
♪I've never let go♪
♪لم أتركه أبدًا♪
[Marriage Certificate]
[شهادة زواج]
♪When I fall♪
♪عندما أسقط♪
♪Please catch me♪
♪أرجوك أمسكني♪
♪Don't say you'll understand♪
♪لا تقل أنك ستفهم♪
♪Hold me tight. Don't let go of this dream♪
♪احتضني بقوة. لا تدع هذا الحلم يفلت منك♪
♪I will wait and embrace what's yet to be♪
♪سأنتظر وأحتضن ما هو قادم♪
♪I've never let go♪
♪لم أتركه أبدًا♪
♪When I fall♪
♪عندما أسقط♪
♪Please catch me♪
♪أرجوك أمسكني♪
♪Don't say you'll understand♪
♪لا تقل أنك ستفهم♪
♪Hold me tight. Don't let go of this dream♪
♪احتضني بقوة. لا تدع هذا الحلم يفلت منك♪
♪I will wait and embrace what's yet to be♪
♪سأنتظر وأحتضن ما هو قادم♪
♪I've never let go♪
♪لم أتركه أبدًا♪
♪When I fall♪
♪عندما أسقط♪
♪Please catch me♪
♪أرجوك أمسكني♪
♪Don't say you'll understand♪
♪لا تقل أنك ستفهم♪
So all these years,
لذلك كل هذه السنوات،
Ji Baijian carried the mystery of his past
جي بايجيان يحمل لغز ماضيه
and the hatred for his parents' deaths.
وكراهيته لموت والديه.
He endured so much suffering I never knew about.
لقد تحمل الكثير من المعاناة التي لم أعرف عنها شيئًا أبدًا.
It must have been really tough and lonely for him all these years.
لا بد أن الأمر كان صعبًا للغاية ووحيدًا بالنسبة له كل هذه السنوات.
Zhizhi.
تشيزهي.
We need to talk.
نحن بحاجة للتحدث.
Okay.
تمام.
Then tell me,
ثم أخبرني
when did you and Ye Taiting acknowledge each other?
متى اعترفت أنت ويي تايتينغ ببعضكما البعض؟
A while ago.
منذ فترة.
That long ago.
منذ زمن طويل.
Then why didn't you tell me?
إذن لماذا لم تخبرني؟
Nothing to tell.
لا يوجد شيء لأقوله.
It's not something to be proud of.
إنه ليس شيئاً يدعو للفخر.
Then
ثم
why did you help him?
لماذا ساعدته؟
I wasn't helping him.
لم أكن أساعده.
I was helping myself.
كنت أساعد نفسي.
You collaborated with Ji Baijian
لقد تعاونت مع جي بايجيان
on the Drizzt project
حول مشروع Drizzt
without telling me either.
دون أن يخبرني أيضًا.
Zhizhi.
تشيزهي.
Haven't you sensed
ألم تشعر
my feelings for you at all?
ما هي مشاعري تجاهك على الإطلاق؟
Ever since I came to the Song family,
منذ أن جئت إلى عائلة سونغ،
you were the closest person to me.
لقد كنت أقرب شخص لي.
Then I've developed feelings for you over time.
ثم لقد طورت مشاعر تجاهك بمرور الوقت.
But I knew I was beneath you.
ولكنني كنت أعلم أنني أقل منك.
So I buried my feelings.
لذلك دفنت مشاعري.
But by the time I found the courage
ولكن بحلول الوقت الذي وجدت فيه الشجاعة
to stand before you,
للوقوف أمامك،
you'd already fallen for Ji Baijian!
لقد وقعت بالفعل في حب جي بيجيان!
I thought once you knew what he'd done,
اعتقدت أنه بمجرد أن تعرف ما فعله،
you'd leave him.
سوف تتركه.
I thought if I had done well enough,
اعتقدت أنه لو فعلت ذلك بشكل جيد بما فيه الكفاية،
you'd finally see me.
سوف تراني أخيرا.
But you?
ولكن انت؟
You're still entangled with him! Why?
مازلتِ متورطة معه! لماذا؟
Why is he the only one
لماذا هو الوحيد
who can affect you like this,
من يمكنه التأثير عليك بهذه الطريقة؟
and not me?
وليس انا؟
What does he have that I don't?
ماذا لديه ولا أملكه؟
Ziming,
زيمينج،
it's not about who has more or less.
لا يتعلق الأمر بمن لديه أكثر أو أقل.
We grew up together.
لقد نشأنا معًا.
I see you as a brother.
أراك كأخ.
I...
أنا...
Brother?
أخ؟
I thought about protecting you
لقد فكرت في حمايتك
for a lifetime as your brother.
طوال حياتك كأخ لك.
But not anymore.
ولكن ليس بعد الآن.
Why does Ji Baijian get to have you,
لماذا يحصل جي بايجيان علىك؟
and I don't?
وأنا لا؟
Ziming.
زيمينج.
You're frightening me right now.
أنت تخيفني الآن.
It was my weakness that made me lose you.
لقد كان ضعفي هو الذي جعلني أفقدك.
Not anymore.
ليس بعد الآن.
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Zhizhi.
تشيزهي.
Stay away from me!
ابتعد عني!
Wei Ziming.
وي زيمينج.
If that's how you want it,
إذا كان هذا هو ما تريد،
from now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
we'll go our separate ways!
سوف نذهب في طرقنا المنفصلة!
We have nothing to do with each other anymore!
لم يعد لدينا أي علاقة مع بعضنا البعض!
♪Honestly, I don't care♪
♪ بصراحة، لا يهمني ♪
♪How many times you've hurt me♪
♪كم مرة جرحتني♪
♪What you call sincere devotion♪
♪ما تسميه التفاني الصادق♪
♪Maybe I've just grown numb♪
♪ربما أصبحت مخدرًا للتو♪
♪Honestly, I don't care♪
♪ بصراحة، لا يهمني ♪
♪Even if I've strayed♪
♪حتى لو ضللت الطريق♪
♪I'm still crying for someone♪
♪مازلت أبكي من أجل شخص ما♪
♪Crying over losing to♪
♪البكاء على الخسارة أمام♪
♪My own pride♪
♪فخري الخاص♪
♪The wind breaks the withered tree♪
♪الريح تكسر الشجرة الذابلة♪
♪It's too weak to be propped up anymore♪
♪إنه ضعيف جدًا بحيث لا يمكن دعمه بعد الآن♪
♪Scenes of the past replay again and again♪
♪مشاهد من الماضي تتكرر مرارا وتكرارا♪
♪Tired of being weak and helpless♪
♪تعبت من الضعف والعجز♪
♪Honestly, I don't care♪
♪ بصراحة، لا يهمني ♪
♪Maybe it's a kind of gift♪
♪ربما يكون هذا نوع من الهدية♪
♪Bitterness helps me comprehend♪
♪المرارة تساعدني على الفهم♪
Fine.
بخير.
♪The path that still lies ahead♪
♪الطريق الذي لا يزال أمامنا♪
I'll just have to make you mine
سوف اضطر إلى جعلك ملكي
in my own way.
بطريقتي الخاصة.
Ziming,
زيمينج،
I want to hold a party tomorrow.
أريد أن أقيم حفلة غدا.
I'm going to let everyone know that you're my son.
سأخبر الجميع أنك ابني.
Understood.
مفهومة.
I'll get ready.
سأستعد.
Also,
أيضًا،
I'd like to
انا ارغب في ذلك
talk with you about some internal matters
التحدث معك حول بعض الأمور الداخلية
to prepare you for joining the higher-ups.
لتحضيرك للانضمام إلى المستويات الأعلى.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
don't sign that second contract
لا توقع على هذا العقد الثاني
Song Zhizhi gave you.
أعطاك أغنية Zhizhi.
It's a trap.
إنه فخ.
You're sharp, Ziming.
أنت حاد، زيمينغ.
Whatever you say.
مهما قلت.
I have one request.
عندي طلب واحد.
Name it. I'll agree to whatever you say.
سمّها، وسأوافق على أي شيء تقوله.
I want to return to Starlight Jewelry.
أريد العودة إلى Starlight Jewelry.
Ms. Song, please take a look.
السيدة سونغ، من فضلك ألقي نظرة.
I think the color gradient on these two pieces
أعتقد أن تدرج الألوان في هاتين القطعتين
should be similar to the ones over here.
يجب أن تكون مشابهة لتلك الموجودة هنا.
We just need to adjust this part.
نحن بحاجة فقط إلى تعديل هذا الجزء.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Ms. Song, Mr. Wei is here.
السيدة سونغ، السيد وي هنا.
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Mr. Wei has recently received an appointment from the group.
لقد حصل السيد وي مؤخرًا على تعيين من المجموعة.
As the special commissioner,
بصفتي المفوض الخاص،
Mr. Wei will specifically assist and handle
سوف يقوم السيد وي بالمساعدة والتعامل بشكل خاص
all major matters at Starlight Jewelry.
جميع الأمور الرئيسية في Starlight Jewelry.
From now on, all personnel changes and major decisions
من الآن فصاعدا، سيتم اتخاذ جميع التغييرات في الموظفين والقرارات الرئيسية
at Starlight Jewelry
في مجوهرات ستارلايت
will need his approval and oversight.
سوف تحتاج إلى موافقته وإشرافه.
Special commissioner?
مفوض خاص؟
If I recall correctly,
إذا كنت أتذكر بشكل صحيح،
Starlight Jewelry is primarily controlled by the Song family.
شركة Starlight Jewelry تخضع في المقام الأول لسيطرة عائلة Song.
Since when do we need a special commissioner
منذ متى نحتاج إلى مفوض خاص؟
coming in to dictate terms?
هل يأتي أحد ليفرض الشروط؟
Times have changed.
لقد تغيرت الأوقات.
Starlight Jewelry needs the group's backing
تحتاج مجوهرات ستارلايت إلى دعم المجموعة
if you're going to bid for the Drizzt project.
إذا كنت تنوي التقدم بعطاء لمشروع Drizzt.
Since the group is providing substantial
نظرًا لأن المجموعة تقدم خدمات كبيرة
funding and resources,
التمويل والموارد،
it will supervise the daily management
وسوف يشرف على الإدارة اليومية
of Starlight Jewelry.
من مجوهرات ستارلايت.
Looking forward to working together.
نتطلع للعمل معًا.
[Invitation to Starlight Group Party]
[دعوة لحضور حفل مجموعة ستارلايت]
What's this?
ما هذا؟
An internal party of Starlight Group.
حزب داخلي لمجموعة ستارلايت.
Tonight, Ye Taiting will announce
الليلة، سوف يعلن يي تايتينغ
that I am his son.
أني ابنه.
So you stabbed me in the back
لذلك طعنتني في الظهر
because you found out
لأنك اكتشفت
Ye Taiting is your father. Is that it?
يي تايتينغ هو أبوك. أهذا هو؟
If I'm not mistaken,
إذا لم أكن مخطئا،
my failed contract with Ye Taiting
عقدي الفاشل مع يي تايتينغ
was also your doing, wasn't it?
وكان هذا أيضًا من فعلك، أليس كذلك؟
It's only natural
إنه أمر طبيعي
I'd warn my father against signing
سأحذر والدي من التوقيع
a risky contract.
عقد محفوف بالمخاطر.
But Zhizhi,
لكن زيزهي
I told you I'd protect you.
لقد قلت لك أنني سأحميك.
That promise still stands.
ولا زال هذا الوعد قائما.
If you're with me,
إذا كنت معي،
Starlight Jewelry will always be yours.
مجوهرات ستارلايت ستكون دائما لك.
But if you're still acting like you were yesterday,
ولكن إذا كنت لا تزال تتصرف كما لو كنت بالأمس،
then I'll handle everything
ثم سأتولى كل شيء
by the book from now on.
حسب الكتاب من الآن فصاعدا.
♪When your lies and indifference♪
♪عندما تكذب ولا مبالاتك♪
♪Pierce my heart and shatter it♪
♪اخترق قلبي وحطمه♪
♪All my piety and persistence♪
♪كل تقواي ومثابرتي♪
♪Are torn apart, turning into bubbles in the air♪
♪تتمزق وتتحول إلى فقاعات في الهواء♪
♪When my fairy tale is broken by you♪
♪عندما تحطم حكايتي الخيالية بسببك♪
♪Turning into nightmares that haunt me♪
♪تتحول إلى كوابيس تطاردني♪
♪I decide to break free from your shackles♪
♪قررت أن أتحرر من قيودك♪
♪No longer swallowing the poison apple♪
♪ لم يعد يبتلع تفاحة السم ♪
♪You fed me♪
♪لقد أطعمتني♪
♪I burn the fairy tale, rewrite the role♪
♪أحرق الحكاية الخيالية، وأعيد كتابة الدور♪
♪Reborn as a resolute me♪
♪ولدت من جديد كشخصية حازمة♪
♪I have broken free from your shackles♪
♪لقد تحررت من قيودك♪
♪Throwing away that poison apple♪
♪رمي تلك التفاحة المسمومة♪
♪You fed me♪
♪لقد أطعمتني♪
♪From this moment on, I no longer care♪
♪من هذه اللحظة فصاعدا، لم أعد أهتم♪
♪No more noise in my ears♪
♪لا مزيد من الضوضاء في أذني♪
♪That's the peace I've always yearned for♪
♪هذا هو السلام الذي كنت أشتاق إليه دائمًا♪
♪Who was I trying to change for?♪
♪من كنت أحاول التغيير من أجله؟♪
♪Smiling, crying, complaining♪
♪يبتسم، يبكي، يشكو♪
♪That's the contentment I should learn to embrace♪
♪هذا هو الرضا الذي يجب أن أتعلم احتضانه♪
♪Honestly, I don't care♪
♪ بصراحة، لا يهمني ♪
♪How many times you've hurt me♪
♪كم مرة جرحتني♪
♪What you call sincere devotion♪
♪ما تسميه التفاني الصادق♪
♪Maybe I've just grown numb♪
♪ربما أصبحت مخدرًا للتو♪
♪Honestly, I don't care♪
♪ بصراحة، لا يهمني ♪
♪Even if I've strayed♪
♪حتى لو ضللت الطريق♪
♪I'm still crying for someone♪
♪مازلت أبكي من أجل شخص ما♪
♪Crying over losing to my own pride♪
♪ البكاء على الخسارة أمام كبريائي ♪